[{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678896089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5232,"timeElapsed":77845},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678898931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2840,"timeElapsed":80688},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678901486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2553,"timeElapsed":83243},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678905977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4490,"timeElapsed":87734},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678908742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2764,"timeElapsed":90499},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678912638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3894,"timeElapsed":94395},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678915508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2869,"timeElapsed":97265},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678918001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2491,"timeElapsed":99758},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678920787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2785,"timeElapsed":102544},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678926735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4843,"timeElapsed":108492},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678929210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2473,"timeElapsed":110967},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678931443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2232,"timeElapsed":113200},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678934514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3070,"timeElapsed":116271},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678936280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1765,"timeElapsed":118037},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678938466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2184,"timeElapsed":120223},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678940796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":122553},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678943174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2377,"timeElapsed":124931},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678945210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2035,"timeElapsed":126967},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678949821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3419,"timeElapsed":131578},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678953218,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3396,"timeElapsed":134975},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678955360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2140,"timeElapsed":137117},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2118,"timeElapsed":139236},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678960378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2898,"timeElapsed":142135},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678962474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2095,"timeElapsed":144231},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678964264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1789,"timeElapsed":146021},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2054,"timeElapsed":148076},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678968373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2053,"timeElapsed":150130},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678970920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2546,"timeElapsed":152677},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678976840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4177,"timeElapsed":158597},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678978555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1714,"timeElapsed":160312},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678980465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1909,"timeElapsed":162222},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678982450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1985,"timeElapsed":164207},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678984526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2075,"timeElapsed":166283},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678986444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1917,"timeElapsed":168201},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678987944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1499,"timeElapsed":169701},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2898,"timeElapsed":172601},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678992982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2137,"timeElapsed":174739},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":6025,"timeElapsed":181829},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679001786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1713,"timeElapsed":183543},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679003976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2188,"timeElapsed":185733},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2028,"timeElapsed":187762},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679007309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1303,"timeElapsed":189066},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2032,"timeElapsed":191099},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679010480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1137,"timeElapsed":192237},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679011772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1291,"timeElapsed":193529},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679013599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1825,"timeElapsed":195356},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679020558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5902,"timeElapsed":202315},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2203,"timeElapsed":204520},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679024600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1835,"timeElapsed":206357},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679027021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":208778},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679028667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1646,"timeElapsed":210424},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679030011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1343,"timeElapsed":211768},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1945,"timeElapsed":213715},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679034027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2068,"timeElapsed":215784},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679035634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1606,"timeElapsed":217391},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679041149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4162,"timeElapsed":222906},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679043232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2081,"timeElapsed":224989},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679044918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1685,"timeElapsed":226675},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679046970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2051,"timeElapsed":228727},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679048155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1184,"timeElapsed":229912},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1335,"timeElapsed":231248},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1356,"timeElapsed":232605},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679052359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1510,"timeElapsed":234116},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1565,"timeElapsed":235683},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4686,"timeElapsed":241706},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":243792},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1794,"timeElapsed":245588},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679065830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1999,"timeElapsed":247587},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679068565,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":250322},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1891,"timeElapsed":252214},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679071891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1432,"timeElapsed":253647},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679074591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2699,"timeElapsed":256348},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":258470},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679078848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2134,"timeElapsed":260605},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679083155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3028,"timeElapsed":264912},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2060,"timeElapsed":266973},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":268780},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679089299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2274,"timeElapsed":271056},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2119,"timeElapsed":273176},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679093281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1860,"timeElapsed":275038},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2002,"timeElapsed":277040},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679097246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1961,"timeElapsed":279002},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2043,"timeElapsed":281047},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2863,"timeElapsed":285072},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1757,"timeElapsed":286831},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679107220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2145,"timeElapsed":288977},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679109096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1874,"timeElapsed":290853},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679110688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1591,"timeElapsed":292445},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679114938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4249,"timeElapsed":296695},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1944,"timeElapsed":298640},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679118808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1924,"timeElapsed":300565},{"subjectID":"hutb3nmvpb","prolificID":"6669fe44c5660a00d14ab11d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b448766ef753065b3f8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679121566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2757,"timeElapsed":303323}]